Music
Hello or good evening everyone, this is Takashiya.
Yes, that's right.
I'd like to do an unannounced clothes check in the Yade-san room.
I'd like to do this without telling the members in advance, and just hit them when they come to the rehearsal.
I would like to check what kind of clothes they usually wear.
This time, there is a plus!
I'd like to predict in advance what I think the members will be wearing.
I'd like to predict in advance what I think this member will be wearing.
There are some members I can imagine.
KAI will be wearing a long black coat.
I think he'll wear a big long coat.
Bare feet and slits.
Lately... KAI often buys what he wants from refamers.
I have an image that KAI often buys what he wants from refamers, so I'm thinking he'll buy what he wants.
Ryoga wears Paul Smith in the top and Zaru in the bottom.
and his pants are monkey.
Socks
His socks are Garamond
and he gets a lot of bullet trains in his bag.
Dandy House hand towels that you can get on the Shinkansen.
I have a lot of Dandy House hand towels in my bag.
More than I said before
More than I said before.
More than I just said.
More than I just told you
Your room is a mots court
A real mots coat.
Takuya usually wears a hat.
He wears a hat that hides all his hair.
Sometimes his shoes have tabio in them.
I think he might be a sneak thief.
I'm sorry it took me so long to be brave.
I'm sorry I'm a little late, but...
I sent a birthday present to your family just the other day.
I sent it home. I sent them home.
They've been coming over quite a bit lately, so...
I'm guessing that when they come tomorrow
I'm guessing he'll be wearing it when he comes tomorrow.
The base color is navy.
It's partially finished with checks.
I'm thinking it'll be like a long coat.
It's as if he's going to go hushing up now.
A lot of convenience store bags
I think he's going to bring such a big convenience store bag.
That's my guess.
Shu-kun
Shu-kun is all black.
He'll wear a cloak hat.
Dumbo dumbo pants...
Markon will wear a buckha
He's going to wear big shoes.
We've been rehearsing a lot lately.
I'm thinking, "How often do they buy these things?
I think they're eating...
I've seen you buy some kind of simmered mackerel
I have an image of you buying it at the convenience store.
The other day at rehearsal
He had everything in his hand.
I brought it with me.
And he's like a suit.
He's got a mackerel in one hand.
I'm thinking he'll be wearing that style tomorrow.
Aloha is like Balenciaga's outerwear.
Like Balenciaga's outerwear.
I'm going to get some Famichiki.
Glasses.
I have some glasses here.
He writes like this.
Sometimes... like this.
She writes like a grandmother.
Lastly, spring.
I thought she'd wear a backpack in the spring. I thought maybe I'd wear some kind of backpack in the spring.
In the side pocket of the backpack.
I'm betting he's got a folding umbrella in the side pocket of his backpack.
There's a dog in the back butt pocket.
I'm thinking he'll put on a pair of Demim painted pants
I'm thinking he's going to put on a pair of Demim painted pants.
I'm betting that he's going to buy something with chocolate on it.
I'm sure there's chocolate on something.
Good morning.
It's 9:00 this morning.
And then we're going to rehearsal.
So I'm heading to the studio now.
We'll see how everyone reacts and then we'll go over the answers.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much for your time.
Wait a minute.
What?
Come forward a little bit.
Oh! You're right about one thing!
Oh! Unannounced dress check.
Wow!
Of course.
I was just doing a spot-check on my own.
I knew it was coming.
This is what he'll be wearing.
Wow, that wasn't a real mots coat.
Mott's coat?
I thought he'd wear a mots coat.
Oh! I was right about the hat.
I always wear it that way.
I see.
That's exactly what I thought you'd do.
What a surprise!
Isn't it amazing? I wore this today.
You've seen it before, right?
I don't remember this.
No, this is the jacket I'm wearing, and I thought it was so cute, I made it easy on both of us by asking for another one.
I thought it was cute, so I asked for another one for both of us. I'll get you another one... and another lease.
Who's the first person to be picked up at the first station?
Who's that?
Who's your name?
I'm not going to stop you...
Nice!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Good work, sir.
Good evening.
I'm just a little ahead of you.
Oh, hey, let me just answer a few questions.
Come to the front a little bit.
Gachimotsu, he was over here.
I was over here.
Just a little bit up front, up front
Unannounced, personal appearance check.
Mr. Yataro's rule.
Oh, is it over?
Clothes check.
I was expecting you to dress like this.
I might not be right at all.
By the way, Spring, today...
It's a convenience store bag.
Can I see what's inside?
All the way in?
Oh, my God.
I didn't buy any chocolate.
Looks good.
I've been patient.
It's the one day I don't have to wear black.
I'm going all black.
Denim.
It's a little more colorful.
Striped knit.
After all, Yuki...
He brings a big convenience store bag.
on the other hand...On the contrary.
It's a big package.
I thought maybe you'd wear something like a checked coat.
I thought maybe he'd wear something like a checked coat.
This one is all black.
I thought he'd come in all black.
That's unusual.
On the contrary, it's unusual.
I changed Sakuya's pants.
He was wearing these, right?
They look like mine.
That's why I wore them today.
From Barillas Valencia.
Mihara? Mihara Rick Valencia?
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Sorry.
Good morning.
Hey! Can I ask you to come forward?
The one who did Mr. Yase's unannounced memory check.
I see.
First of all, this is today. Aloha.
You mean the short Balenciaga down jacket?
Yes, yes, yes.
It's long, isn't it?
It's quite long. Not at all.
But it's a little warm.
Yes, indeed. It's warm today.
In terms of the concept of today's outfit...
Today...
I'm going to dress like a beauty.
Exactly!
And I'm wearing my horseshoes.
And I recently bought these new pants.
Really?
I always wear pants that are too thick.
I'm getting used to them.
Good morning. Oh, good morning.
Good morning
Takashi Moon House
Oh, sorry.
Thank you at all
Oh, yeah.
Go buy some komichiki today.
Go get some.
Go buy some.
I see.
We're doing an unannounced clothes check.
By the way, today Kai...
Well...
I bought what I wanted.
Not today.
Nothing today?
I can't believe how hard it is to win.
It's like a slip-on.
I thought it would come like a slip-on
It wasn't a slip-on
It wasn't a slip-on.
They weren't slip-ons.
It was yesterday, wasn't it?
You know what?
They're all those things.
Black.
It's pretty smart.
I didn't expect that today.
This is so warm.
It's warm, isn't it?
It's warm because of what you're wearing.
I don't know.
Seriously.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's so scary.
I can wear it without hesitation
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
You got me all worked up.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Sorry.
Oui.
Thank you for watching.
Good morning.
Wait a minute.
I'm...
I'm in Yase's room.
Scary, scary, scary...
Unannounced checks.
First...
Bucket hat correct.
Yes, bucket hat.
I knew you'd wear it.
And the big shoes.
He's wearing big shoes.
The kind of shoes that make your pants hang up.
Yes. No.
I got two hits.
Oh, my God.
That's new.
They just did a spot check on me.
No, I'm not wearing that.
I'm not wearing... I'm not wearing...
I'm not wearing any clothes.
They're all from years ago.
Taken.
Taken. swallowed
Yes, sir.
It's pretty neat.
I see something in your bag.
What is it?
Don't make a face.
No, no, no...
I didn't make it.
I'm not working on it.
We have one more goal.
We have three goals.
This is what we're going to wear.
And these are the things we're going to buy.
for the rehearsal.
We're trying to figure it out right now.
Two of the things we're doing are bucket hats and
Which one? Which one?
And the other one is on the mark.
I'm getting a mackerel.
Wow, that makes sense.
I didn't buy it today.
You didn't.
But every day for the past week or so.
I've heard you say you bought fish.
I didn't have any today, so I didn't buy much.
I thought I'd have some tonight.
Wow, that's a lot of fish for three pieces.
So you were definitely eating until yesterday.
That's why I expected it.
The last one was Ryoga.
I was expecting it.
I don't understand.
The top one is Paul Smith.
And the bottom pants are Zara.
Well then... Then so be it.
This is
This is Paul Smith.
That's right.
I think that's Paul Smith, too.
It doesn't say "Paul Smith," but...
This one's also Paul Smith.
But just in case, this is Paul Smith, too.
Paul Smith, above.
No, but I still don't know.
Bottom Zara
What does it say?
Is it written anywhere?
It doesn't exist.
This is the kind you wear in a package.
I don't get it.
Zara! It's all the way down!
It's all the way up.
It's more like this.
The socks are wearing Garamond.
Gala? But is it a gala?
Socks for rehearsal.
Did you already wear socks for rehearsal?
For when you go home.
For when you go home, usually for casual wear.
Garamond
I wore Garamonds.
Oh, man!
I'm getting a really good hit here.
Beautiful.
It's the last one.
No, but it looks like his bag might have been a little damaged.
What? Wait a minute.
The end.
The last one?
There's a lot of Dandy Houses in that bag.
I wonder if I'm getting a new curser.
I hope not.I don't know if I did.
I just changed my dandy bag.
I just changed my bag.
Yeah, that's why I'm a little unsure of myself.
Wow, you tell me.
Don't tell me.
I'll tell you!
Dandy house
A place to say it A place to say it
Say it.
No! No!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I didn't think it was that much.
A hundred.
No way. All of it.
100 points.
No way. The whole amount.
100 points
Oh no.
It was implemented.
Thank you.
That's great.
So how were the other members, by the way?
The others didn't hit me at all.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
We were guessed so well.
Just as I expected.
As expected.
I don't know.
I don't think it's gonna be the food.
I don't think it's going to be food.
Fish.
Yeah, I was going to guess.
I was going to guess, but I didn't get it right.
Even if I had, it wouldn't have been a surprise.
Basically, everyone Basically, I knew it, guys.
Cirque is cool!
Silk is cool!
Like this
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
That was the unannounced silk check.